{
    "id": "828e08f0f6384b989962a8ab9b3c8f05",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Our General Manager, .......................................... has retired, is planning to go abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6af46a4f5c2f47cda6d5aad09fbad64b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our child, ........................................... has no appetite for food, should be taken to the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb880d8a79a24d8a877bc4a31f2e5255"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother, ............................................... can’t read or write, used to tell me a lot of stories.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd58b96aa2f44b19ab9ef9e8e95a3d77"
        },
        {
            "question": "This medicine, ........................................................ was prescribed by a native doctor, relieves pain instantly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a5148f22e7e4dd5a8e061cc6c609e28"
        },
        {
            "question": "My friend Charles, ................................................. was very dear to me, passed away last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8955269ff8e743bdbb467de85dd4d230"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met with an accident about ................................................... I shall tell you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cdd07d1050fa44029b3c8578ad9d6d8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to consult the doctor ................................................. treated me last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "who",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "32dffd2d32d749b58af5ad3f1a13ce0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our grandmother told us a story .................................................. we had not heard before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1e7143f8e25441f92ee47b5d9ac6536"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of the boys ................................................... went on the study tour is missing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "18a5ec71305744e8a90e68ecf366a1b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Students ................................................ belong to the Scheduled Castes and Tribes don’t have to pay the application fee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09afcc94c2684b13a771275da4196f57"
        }
    ]
}